manacrystals.com 2016-11-10

# Privacy Policy | Mana Crystals

Privacy is important. We respect yours. Our goal is to do more than we have to by law — we want to earn your trust that we are careful with your data.

### General information

This policy sets out our privacy practices and explains how we handle the information we collect when you visit and use our sites, services, products, and content (“Services”).

### What we may collect

We collect information about what Mana Crystals pages you access, information about your mobile device (such as device or browser type), information you send us (such as an email address used to register or communicate with us), and referral information.

When you use Mana Crystals Services, we may collect and store your Internet Protocol address. We may use this information to fight spam and other abuse; to personalize Mana Crystals Services; or to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how people use Mana Crystals Services.

### Emails

We won’t email you to ask for your password or other account information. If you receive such an email, send it to us so we can investigate.

### Disclosure of your information

We don’t share your personal information outside the company.

We won’t sell your personal information.

We may share your personal information with third parties in limited circumstances, including: (1) with your consent; (2) to a vendor or partner who meets our data protection standards; or (3) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process.

We use cookies and similar technologies such as pixels and local storage to recognize you when you return to our Services. We use them in various ways, for example to log you in, remember your preferences (such as default language), evaluate email effectiveness, show relevant ads, and personalize information.

We respect Do Not Track (“DNT”) settings in browsers. If you’re logged out of our Services and have DNT enabled, we will not set cookies. You can’t log into Mana Crystals while DNT is enabled.

Some third-party services that we use, such as embedly or Google Analytics, may place their own cookies in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by Mana Crystals only and not the use of cookies by third parties.

### Data Storage

Mana Crystals uses third-party vendors and hosting partners, such as Amazon, for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology we need to run Mana Crystals. We maintain two types of logs: server logs and event logs.

### Modifying your personal information

If you have a Mana Crystals account, you can access and modify your personal information [here](https://manacrystals.com/account/profile/edit).

### Data security

We use encryption (HTTPS) to protect data transmitted to and from our site. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, so we can’t guarantee security. You use the Service at your own risk, and you’re responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account (like using a strong password).

### Changes to this Policy

Mana Crystals may periodically update this Policy. We’ll notify you about significant changes to it. The most current version of the policy will always be here and we will archive former versions of the policy here.

### Questions

We welcome questions, concerns, and feedback about this policy at [support@manacrystals.com](mailto:support@manacrystals.com).
